

CONTACT ME AT

- Svitákova 2818/9, 155 00 Prague Czech Republic
- pergler.vladislav@gmail.com
- +420 777 343 781

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Analytics and Research
- • • Project Management
- ••• Business Development
- ••• Budgeting and Cost planning
- • • Process Improvement
- •••• Agile

LANGUAGES

- •••• English
- •••• Czech
- •••• Russian
- •••• German

CERTIFICATIONS

- Harvard Business School Online
 CORe (2019)
- British Council CAE (2018)

VLADISLAV PERGLER

CONSULTANT IN AUTOMOTIVE & MOBILITY

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced business consultant with 4+ years of experience in business operations and strategy in Automotive and Finance. Familiar with all stages of project design and implementation. Strong analytic and research skills. Highly motivated with a focus on the delivery of results and value-added for the clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Consultant in Automotive & Mobility (Full-time)

Ernst&Young | 2019 - present

- Participating in day-to-day project coordination, stakeholder alignment, planning, implementation and delivery
- Projects for automotive OEMs: Digital transformation, Change management, Fleet app development, Market research, New business formats, Sales personnel training
- Business development: Car price index, CRM system development and implementation

Audit Trainee (Full-time)

PriceWaterhouseCoopers | 2017 - 2018

- Assessing accuracy, completeness and classification of various general ledger accounts
- Auditing by IFRS and US GAAP standards

Sales Manager Assistant (Part-time)

Mercedes-Benz Financial Services | 2016 - 2017

- Sales of finance and insurance products to customers
- Active communication with dealership network and contracts closing

Project Manager Assistant (Internship)

ŠKODA AUTO | 2015 - 2016

- Assisting in coordination of all activities related to markets -Ukraine and Kazakhstan
- Analysis of new potential markets and business development

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

University of Economics in Prague

Masters in International Business | 2018 - December 2021

- Exchange semester in EBS Universität für Wirtschaft und Recht (Germany)
- Studied international business, automotive management, M&A, start-up & new business model development
- Bachelor in International Business (2014-2018)